hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft it's
dangerous to fly like this because you
really can't tell where you're going we
are starting off in the mini game
district and we're not going to be
playing mini games and we're also not
building mini games
we're actually going to be working on
our method of selling some sahara now
memberships and since this is the hip
and happening and hoppiness area in the
entire server right now everyone's
either making mini games or is over in
area 77 what i thought i would do is
make a big billboard style thing to
promote
the sales of sahara now and i've even
now come up with a bunch of these boxes
which i'm going to try and sell so the
way that i plan on getting memberships
from everyone is by showing them
examples of the kind of deals they can
expect from sahara now and then when
they give me the hundred diamonds i will
actually go and put all of these boxes
in the system so that they can cycle
through i know that iskal said that uh
that they don't know what they're gonna
buy
i think that's a terrible idea so look
at this i'm gonna show them look these
are the kind of deals you can expect so
we've got the hungry box for eight
diamonds eight diamonds you get the
shulker box
and all of the golden carrots bearing in
mind that's one diamond two three four
five six seven eight so you get about
you get a shulker box and half a box
carrots for free
uh you get to the moon five diamonds for
a box of fireworks
all sorts you get four diamonds and you
get all of this
another another box full of stuff it's
quartz this time for five diamonds that
is a really really good deal
and then a box of gravel also for four
diamonds so these are some insane prices
this is basically giving it away but
these are the kinds of things that we
need to be selling in saharan now to get
people to buy the membership so let's
start by building this giant billboard
ready to sell these boxes and hopefully
i'll be the one to get the most
memberships out of everybody
oh
boy
strap yourselves in put your seatbelt on
and adjust your chair because this is no
billboard this is a giant blimp and i'm
doing what no builder should do which is
eyeballing this i didn't go into
creative i didn't plan this i looked up
a picture of a blimp specifically from
the movie up you know the spirit of
adventure
and i just went for it
unfortunately
i thought it would take a tiny amount of
time i'll let you know after this time
lapse is done exactly how long it took
but this is one of the most complicated
shapes to make ever because it's not a
cylinder and it's not just a sphere at
the front it's a very custom shape where
it gets slightly smaller at the back but
it's very circular at the front this was
literally the hardest thing that i've
ever built on the hermitcraft server and
i 100
regret making it i should have gone for
something much easier but i had
committed and i was gonna finish it so
i'd made the giant blimp part so that
was the hardest part and then i went and
made all of the fins i made the bit
underneath which is the only bit
actually is going to get used which is
hilarious and then i had to go and get
people's attention with the giant
question mark putting some giant
propellers on it and then a big red
arrow but guess how long this took
i'm a bit of a broken hermit after this
project i'm not gonna lie
two hours i said
two hours this will take you'll get this
done in time for your next episode
no i didn't
this took 12 hours probably over 12
hours because i didn't record every
second of it but my goodness
are we gonna sell some memberships so
we've got a big advertising blimp here
now now it's not particularly obvious in
fact it's got a giant question mark on
it that insinuates
that you're not supposed to know what
this is about and i've even put a giant
red arrow if that doesn't get people's
attention that are working in
hermitville or new hermitville or the
hippie area or area 77 or the mini game
district all the different lands
they're going to see this it's so
enormous
and eye-catching
that i would immediately see that giant
question mark what's this about giant
red arrow yes please
and then you go inside and you find
nothing so i haven't built anything here
yet but i am
about to add it so what we're going to
do
is just set this up because what we're
doing here is trying to sell
memberships that's the big thing
memberships
so this is going to be my armor stand
green when i get a green head he's the
captain of this here airship and he's
here to sell you some sahara memberships
so it's true i spent 12 hours building
something just to get people's attention
i probably could have done this in a
much better way a much much better way
but it will all be worth it if i sell
the most memberships for sahara because
of it this is my big advertising thing
this is where all the budget for my my
sahara advertising scheme is the giant
mystery balloon and here's the genius
part i'm showing them potential deals
none of these deals are actually in
sahara at all okay none of them none of
these deals actually exist in sahara
they will do later when i've sold the
memberships these will definitely be
added into the system so this should
entice people to get to have a look and
see oh my goodness eight diamonds for
all of this plus the shulker box now i
have to remind people that these aren't
for sale we'll put the captain here in
shining armor there we go captain green
welcome aboard okay so we've got our
sahara now member here and it costs 100
diamonds we're not allowed to offer any
discount that's part of the rules and
we're not allowed to show them what is
in sahara now already it's meant to be
blind but as much as i hate it i'm gonna
have to write a book to explain this
because there's
i need people to buy this and hopefully
hopefully they'll just read it because
there's too much information so let's
write this book okay so it says sahara
now membership glad i got your attention
with my enormous blimp i am here to show
you some of the best deals you can get
with a sahara now membership you simply
buy a token from me here and take it to
the sahara in the shopping district you
gain access to the upstairs area where
you can cycle through shulker boxes like
you see here the prices are low each
shulker is unique and the price is for
everything including the shulker box you
will definitely find something you need
at a seriously low price take a look at
my example boxes in the airship to see
the kinds of deals you can expect thanks
for reading and hope you will buy a
membership please buy a membership i
spent so long on this blimp there we go
we're going to sign that
the last thing to do is to add an ender
chest
whoa
excuse me
that was really weird but that that
is pretty much everything this part of
it took about 10 seconds compared to the
actual blimp in fact the inside of this
blimp's pretty big maybe i could do
something with this here let me show you
what's up in here look at this look at
the oh
there's a there's a hole at the back
it's a bit that's a bit awkward there we
go let's just cover cover that up but
like i said there's a huge amount of
space in here that isn't being utilized
so i could possibly do something here
now how did i get in
i know that's i know that iskall has
already sold several of these
memberships so i hope that people
will check this out hopefully the giant
question mark and the big red arrow do
their job as they're supposed to oh
i did only put the um the propellers on
one side basically this just took so
long that i
i started to lose my sanity so i'm gonna
put those on the other side at another
time and hopefully i can use this in the
future as well because when all those
memberships are sold
this becomes a bit useless so maybe i
can do something with it because it's
such an awesome build it'll be shameful
to waste it maybe i can even turn this
into a mini game area at some point oh
that would be awesome you know what i'm
going to do that as soon as all these
memberships are sold i'm going to
convert this into some sort of mini game
it's going to be absolutely awesome all
right
finally finished took way longer and is
probably now the focus of the video but
i do actually need to go back to hippie
land over here because ren is over here
and i need to meet up with him because
it's time to get on board that redstone
hippie we've actually had an applicant
and i've got an idea for it so ren's
online i'm gonna go and message him now
yo ren
you jamming yeah
i'm jamming dude some sweet jeans coming
today okay so uh you saw my my big
hippie rv right in the silo
yes that's my big distraction um for
area 77 but i actually need a bit of
redstone help and
neither of us are pretty good at
redstone so i put an advert out for a
redstone hippie and
one guy applied right
which is what yeah one guy applied so
we're gonna add another hippie to this
commune
if that's if that's cool
i mean one guy though whoops one guy
yeah i mean they'll be fine basically
what i want is like a big countdown
clock but i i've it that's the sort of
thing that sounds like it would be
really easy to do but it turns out it's
really not
okay so who is this guy then yeah
impulse has actually said that he's
super interested in it but since he's
the only applicant i didn't really want
him to think that this was just super
easy and you know just like yeah yeah
you got the job so i'm actually i've
i've borrowed your shroom room and i've
made like a little interview thing so i
just kind of need you to play along
because i'm gonna
i'm just gonna goof with him because
i've made like a little fake interview
for him and i'm just gonna sort of scare
him a little bit make him make him feel
uncomfortable he's gonna put him through
his paces yeah exactly he's going to
think that this is like the most
complicated redstone interview of his
life
i'm just going to answer ask him
nonsense questions but we just got to
pretend like this is super serious all
right okay okay i'm super serious faces
on let's do this he's actually he's
actually online now so i'm just going to
message him and be like yo you ready yo
impulse you want to do that interview
now uh come on over
to the uh
fees
i wonder if he'll be he will be
impressed with my toilet flushing
mechanism because that's some advanced
redstone if i ever did see it the single
piston that you can see the bottom out
listen there's some cabling and a button
involved
i don't know what you're talking about
it's genius raidstudio we need some
redstone help yeah sweet he's on his way
hey guys all right yo okay hey are you
ready for the interview um myself and
rendog are the two uh native hippies
here oh
yeah an interview right um that sounds
super stressful uh okay
impulse we've had many applicants
oh okay this is like our third interview
already so and we've got a photo after
you so don't get your hopes up okay all
right well hey it's worth a shot you
know i have some redstone knowledge and
i thought i could help out so we'll see
we'll see i'll do my best this interview
um requires you to have no blocks on you
so can you empty all your stuff in here
because we're going to provide you with
everything you're going to need
oh yeah sure yeah that's that's not
worrisome at all okay yeah here you go
okay i don't see any flowers do you see
any flowers red oh i see no love no i
see no love this is a this is a this is
not a loved inventory okay right come on
then come on come inside the rv oh wait
all right this is top secret even if you
don't get the job you cannot tell people
what's in here all right come on
got it all right
um i'm coming right so this this here is
the the entrance uh to our uh our layer
but we have a gentleman's rule that you
you don't look because that's you know
that's the done thing i can't go if
you're looking all right so if you would
like to see
okay i'm turning around for a second
right yep okay i'm turned around all
right yeah you can go
all right
my turn you're trying to get no don't
look okay good luck no looking
gentlemen's rules well welcome
welcome to our underground hippie
shroom room
wow if you want to take a seat in the
middle there and we'll begin the
interview because we've got quite a few
questions to get through all right first
of all are you ready
i'm ready yeah all right okay good so
make sure that you're the right man for
the job i need you to select
your favorite flower
flowers um i thought i was here for
redstone
you are this is a redstone question
okay
um i i got i'm totally okay i mean he
doesn't even see it's a redstone
question i mean this is not going
well um all right oh okay uh i'll i
picked this one this one looks pretty
good i like this one right here are you
sure
i don't yeah don't give many hints come
on
pick your favorite flower
it's very colorful i like it yeah go on
like this one yeah that's this one all
right all right all right first question
done um
we've got another few questions for you
so i need you to select
the correct
item correct item for what
yeah the correct item off you go correct
you should know which one's the correct
question okay all right well make you
nervous this is very important
i went with the blue flower last time
i'll go with the blue dye this time
how's that sound this guy right here all
right we've got we've got another one of
these so you went for the blue diamond
that's interesting very interesting um
oh there we go three items for you we
need you to select uh your your favorite
one
yeah well okay now now we're speaking
some redstone finally up my alley right
here of course this is my favorite
redstone block right here the observer
i mean he's making it spin that's pretty
impressive
yeah i don't know you could do that with
redstone
whoa
redstone already okay all right all
right all right i mean i would have
chosen the pickle but yeah i mean yeah
that is that is the the selecting
concluded
are you ready for the music round this
is really really important
i like music yeah i'm gonna play you
three
songs okay
and i want you to tell me which one is
your favorite a b or c are you ready
i'm ready so ah
[Music]
yeah okay right
all right right what do you think
i quite liked that last one see i'm
gonna go with c lock it in okay okay
okay
yeah all right so um if you want to come
over here impulse to this this red thing
here so okay um obviously if you're a
redstone hippie you need to get paid uh
that's that's you know get paid for your
work here uh so i want you to choose how
you would like to get paid
i don't see diamonds as a sign but oh i
ca i suppose i could manage all right um
friendship bro ship
more friendship that sounds like a
winner sign right there i'm gonna pick
more friendship more friendship
more friendship all right is that okay
that's fine no no no no no that's mine
that's right yep all right i'm taking
notes okay i've got one last uh thing
that i need to
to show you so if you want to come to
the back of the interview room uh i've
actually prepared three toilets here for
you and i must admit if you get this one
wrong impulse you do not get the job
okay this is this is a genuine this is
genuine redstone here
i know we've not been taking it too
seriously but this one's genuine
redstone this is a redstone conundrum so
i need you to stand on your favorite
toilet and flush yourself down the
favorite one all right
okay i feel like there's some sort of
trick question here because uh everybody
knows i like quartz but uh you guys
probably like stuff that comes from the
earth more like a wood tone i'm going to
go with this one i'm going to go with
this toilet right here so oh
no
no no i mean i mean yeah i mean
you do you man everything's right and
all you know what i'm gonna i'm gonna go
for it why not
no
oh
seriously
what happened
you you got the job impulse there that
no one else applied
[Laughter]
i thought i've got the job toilet
look you've blushed yourself for the
cause so i think that's enough yeah if
you if you're willing to to die if
you're willing to flush yourself down
the toilet for the hippie cause then uh
you get the job well done well done in
polson excellent all right thank you i
paid the ultimate price for this job
i'll take it
i love how he just went along with our
interview like it was real oh
beautiful it was beautiful oh man
you got me you gotta be good
all right well see you later impulse
enjoy your time yeah
hippie commune first thing tomorrow and
i'll let you know what we're going to be
working on all right
sounds good i'll see you in the morning
well looks like impulses already got
settled in with his giant yellow rv it
looks like he took his inspiration from
someone else's rv if you ask me
that's totally okay i'm sure he's gonna
make it his own has he got anything
inside yet no okay so he's just settled
in he's gonna make his rv uh obviously
he needs to fill it up with everything
so that's awesome and we can help him
out as well but impulse is here for a
reason he's not completely in on all of
our plans but the more he helps us out i
think the more we can trust him and
we'll bring him in on our little secrets
but first i need to give him some uh
instructions on what we need i feel like
i spent most of this episode writing
instructions okay so hey impulse welcome
to the comm you knew i hear because we
need some help you see the giant rv in
the silo outside
yeah it's a thing this is going to
launch in a few days and we need a big
redstone countdown clock facing area 77
built to show how long is left also to
give it a countdown on the day good luck
and welcome aboard hippie green all
right that's his instructions
taken care of
let's get back to what we need to do
which is actually making some of the
tunnels that go into area 77 and we
actually need to make a lot of progress
on our hippie area in general ren is
clearly busy at work
i don't know what he's doing to be
honest but yeah i've got a lot of work
to do here so i think that is all we
have time for today we have got a brand
new hippie we have got a brand new blimp
we are going to sell many memberships
and
whoa
i don't know what that was i don't want
to see it i don't wanna i wanna know
what that is
i don't wanna know what that is
all right thank you very much for
watching and good
bye
you don't even can't even see me here